Yuxin Wen | Curriculum Vitae

 \square +86-136 3236 7603 • \square wen.yuxin@mail.scut.edu.cn

yuxinwen.info • • Yuxin-Wen

Computer Vision | 3D Deep Reconstruction | Adversarial Robustness

OVERVIEW

Being a Ph.D candidate in the fourth year of a five-year educational system in Geometric Perception and Intelligence Research (Gorilla) Lab @SCUT, under the supervision by Prof. Kui Jia, my research interests are in computer vision (to non-Euclidean data) and machine learning, with focus on robustness and generalization analysis of deep neural networks, and deep learning shape modeling and reconstruction of objects and scenes.

EDUCATION

Ph.D candidate

Information and Communication Engineering

Thesis advisor: Prof. Kui Jia

Bachelor's degree

Department of Information Engineering (Elite Class) GPA:3.66/4.00 South China University of Technology

2017.09-present

South China University of Technology

2013.09-2017.06

RECENT PUBLICATION

- [1] M. Yang*, Y. Wen*, W. Chen, Y. Chen, and K. Jia, "Deep Optimized Priors for 3D Shape Modeling and Reconstruction.", in IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2021.
- [2] W. Zhao*, J. Lei*, Y. Wen, J. Zhang, and K. Jia, "Sign-Agnostic Implicit Learning of Surface Self-Similarities for Shape Modeling and Reconstruction from Raw Point Clouds", in *IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2021.
- [3] Y. Wen, J. Lin, K. Chen, C.P. Chen, and K. Jia, "Geometry-aware generation of adversarial point clouds", in IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (TPAMI), 2020.
- [4] Y. Wen*, S. Li*, and K. Jia, "Towards Understanding the Regularization of Adversarial Robustness on Neural Networks", in International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2020.
- [5] K. Jia, S. Li, Y. Wen, T. Liu, and D. Tao. "Orthogonal deep neural networks", in *IEEE transactions on pattern analysis and machine intelligence (TPAMI)*, 2019.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Intern

Serves as an algorithm engineer for 3D reconstruction and detection

DexForce, **Guangzhou** 2020.05-2020.08

Research Assistant

 $Serves\ for\ the\ FDCT\ Funded\ project$

University of Macau, Macau

2019.09-2020.01

SKILLS

Proficient: Python(Pytorch) · LATEX Familiar: C++ · Matlab

AWARDS

2017-20 Academic Scholarship, South China University of Technology 2018 Excellent Student Cadre, South China University of Technology